Okay, time to reveal the results.
さて､ 結果を発表しよう｡
It has run to completion.
完成まで走りきった｡
And here it is.
そしてここにある｡
So a moment to pause.
だから､ ちょっと立ち止まって｡
It turns out that it's actually a little bit worse than the previous results before fine tuning.
実際､ 微調整前の結果よりも少し悪いことが判明した｡
Um, I would expect that.
そうだろうね｡
It's just that it's very similar.
ただ､ とても似ているんだ｡
It's not actually that the model has gotten any worse.
実際､ モデルが悪くなったわけではない｡
I would suspect that fine tuning in this case has not helped us, which is obviously disappointing.
この場合､ 微調整が役に立たなかったのではないかと思う｡
I did warn you at the beginning that there would be a disappointment in this session.
私は冒頭で､ このセッションには残念なことがあると警告した｡
Uh, now, having said that, there are some things that it's definitely improved upon.
とはいえ､ いくつか改善された点もある｡
Unfortunately, they're not reflected in this business metric.
残念ながら､ このビジネス指標には反映されていない｡
Uh, but it has improved in terms of the, the, the biggest outliers.
しかし､ 最も大きな異常値という点では改善されている｡
I don't know if you remember, but when we ran it before, it was guessing some things that were way
覚えているかどうかわからないが､ 以前このテストを実施したときは､ 1000の範囲外のことも推測していた｡
I think I showed you there were points like that were far, far too high.
私は､ そのようなポイントがあまりにも高すぎることを示したと思う｡
And from seeing our data set of 500, it's it's appreciated that there aren't things that are priced
そして､ 500のデータを見たところ､ それほど高い値段のものはないということがわかった｡
And so that has caused something of a, of a nuanced correction to what it's doing.
そのため､ そのようなニュアンスでの修正が行われている｡
But other than that it hasn't particularly helped it.
しかし､ それ以外は特に役に立っていない｡
And in fact, unfortunately with this set, this this test set, at least it's actually appears to have
そして実際､ 残念なことに､ このセット､ このテストセットでは､ 少なくとも､ 我々が本当に注目しているこのビジネス指標である総差異によれば､
hindered it according to this business metric, the one that we're really focused on, the total difference.
実際には妨げになっているように見える｡
So that's a sobering moment for us.
だから､ 私たちにとっては気が重い瞬間だ｡
Uh, and uh, in the next video, I'll explain why.
次のビデオで､ その理由を説明するよ｡
And the times when fine tuning frontier models can be very helpful and when they can't.
また､ フロンティア・モデルの微調整が非常に役立つ時と､ そうでない時がある｡
And fear not, there is, there is, there is good news ahead.
そして､ 恐れることはない｡
Even if this is a is a setback for us, we will we will see more.
たとえこれが後退であったとしても､ 私たちはもっと多くを見ることができるだろう｡
See you next time.
それではまた次回｡